<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="ask_if_record">Do you want to record the operation? </string>
    <string name="expand_ask_if_record">Do you want to confirm recording, skip this recording but perform the action, modify the recording, or cancel this action?</string>

    <string name="disambiguation_error">Can\'t understand your description, please try to describe your action in a different way.</string>
    <string name="disambiguation_error_repeated">Still can\'t understand your description, please try to describe your intention using contents shown on the screen about the object you have clicked on. You can also refer to properties from its values such as \"cheapest\", \"closest\" or \"earliest\". </string>
    <string name="disambiguation_result_wont_match">Your description doesn\'t match what you clicked on, please try again.</string>
    <string name="disambiguation_result_wont_match_repeated">Your description still doesn\'t match what you clicked on, please try to describe your intention using contents shown on the screen about the object you have cliked on. You can also refer to properties in its values such as cheapest, closest or earliest. </string>
    <string name="disambiguation_prompt">Please describe your intention for this action</string>
    <string name="disambiguation_confirm">Is this description correct?</string>
    <!-- <string name="disambiguation_confirm">Is this verbal instruction correct? %1$s</string> -->

    <string name="display_disambiguation_prompt">Please verbally describe your intention for this action</string>



    <string name="disambiguation_followup_prompt">This description matches %1$d items on the screen, Please provide an additional instruction for finding the correct item.</string>
    <string name="disambiguation_followup_no_count_prompt">Please provide an additional description for finding the correct item.</string>
    <string name="disambiguation_choosing_parsing_prompt">Please choose the correct parsing result for your description.</string>


    <string name="edit_textbox_hint">Enter your query here</string>

</resources>
